Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 43 Records, 1889-1968, I.; 49 bound volumes, 23 boxes, 1 official stamp
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1889-1968, I.A; 9 bound volumes, 20 boxes
    - Board Meeting, November 24, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1018)
    - Board Meeting, December 1, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1019)
    - Board Meeting, December 8, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1020)
    - Board Meeting, December 15, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1021)
    - Board Meeting, December 19, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1022)
    - Board Meeting, December 22, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1023)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1024)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1025)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1943, 2 leaves (Box 8, Item 1026)
    - Board Meeting, January 16, 1943, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1027)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1028)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1029)
    - Board Meeting, January 26, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1030)
    - Board Meeting, February 2, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1031)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1032)
    - Board Meeting, February 13, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1033)
    - Board Meeting, February 16, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1034)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1035)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1036)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1037)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1038)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1039)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1040)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1041)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1042)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1043)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1944, 2 leaves (Box 8, Item 1044)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1045)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1046)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1047)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1048)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1049)
    - Board Meeting, June 14, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1050)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1051)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1052)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1053)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1054)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1055)
    - Board Meeting, July 21, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1056)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1057)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1058)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1944, 2 leaves (Box 8, Item 1059)
    - Board Meeting, August 4, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1060)
    - Board Meeting, August 7, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1061)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1062)
    - Board Meeting, August 11, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1063)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1064)
    - Board Meeting, August 17, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1065)
    - Board Meeting, August 18, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1066)
    - Board Meeting, August 24, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1067)
    - Board Meeting, August 25, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1068)
    - Special General Meeting, August 27, 1944, 2 leaves (Box 8, Item 1069)
    - Board Meeting, August 31, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 8, Item 1070)
    - Board Meeting, September 3, 1944, 1 leaves (Box 8, Item 1071)
    - Board Meeting, September 7, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1072)
    - Special General Meeting, September 10, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1073)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1074)
    - Special General Meeting, September 17, 1944, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1075)
    - Board Meeting, September 21, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1076)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1077)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1078)
    - General Meeting, October 11, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1079)
    - Board Meeting, October 12, 1944, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1080)
    - Board Meeting, October 19, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1081)
    - Board Meeting, October 26, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1082)
    - Board Meeting, November 2, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1083)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1084)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1085)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1086)
    - Board Meeting, November 30, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1087)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1088)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 10, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1089)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1090)
    - Board Meeting, December 21, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1091)
    - Board Meeting, December 28, 1944, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1092)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1093)
    - Board Meeting, January 11, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1094)
    - Board Meeting, January 18, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1095)
    - Board Meeting, January 21, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1096)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1097)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1098)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1099)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1100)
    - Board Meeting, February 22, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1101)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1102)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1103)
    - Board Meeting, February 28, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1104)
    - Board Meeting, March 4, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1105)
    - Board Meeting, March 7, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1106)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1107)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1108)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1109)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1110)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1111)
    - Board Meeting, April 10, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1112)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1113)
    - Board Meeting, April 15, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1114)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1115)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1116)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1117)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1118)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1119)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1120)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1121)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1122)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1123)
    - Board Meeting, June 3, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1124)
    - Board Meeting, June 7, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1125)
    - Board Meeting, June 10, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1126)
    - Board Meeting, June 14, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1127)
    - Board Meeting, June 17, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1128)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1129)
    - Board Meeting, June 24, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1130)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1131)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1132)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1133)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1134)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1135)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1136)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1137)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1138)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1139)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1140)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1141)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1142)
    - Special General Meeting, August 19, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1143)
    - Special Board Meeting, August 22, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1144)
    - Board Meeting, August 23, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1145)
    - Special General Meeting, August 26, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1146)
    - Board Meeting, August 29, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1147)
    - Board Meeting, August 30, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1148)
    - Board Meeting, September 1, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1149)
    - Special General Meeting, September 2, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1150)
    - Board Meeting, September 5, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1151)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1152)
    - Special General Meeting, September 9, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1153)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1154)
    - Board Meeting, September 20, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1155)
    - Board Meeting, September 22, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1156)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1157)
    - Board Meeting, September 27, 1945, 3 leaves (Box 9, Item 1158)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1159)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1160)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1161)
    - General Meeting, October 10, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1162)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1163)
    - Board Meeting, October 12, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1164)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1165)
    - Board Meeting, October 20, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1166)
    - Board Meeting, October 25, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1167)
    - Board Meeting, October 27, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1168)
    - Board Meeting, November 1, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1169)
    - Special General Meeting, November 4, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1170)
    - Board Meeting, November 8, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1171)
    - Board Meeting, November 10, 1945, 3 leaves (Box 9, Item 1172)
    - Board Meeting, November 12, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1173)
    - Board Meeting, November 13, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1174)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1945, 2 leaves (Box 9, Item 1175)
    - Board Meeting, November 24, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1176)
    - Special General Meeting, November 25, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1177)
    - Board Meeting, November 27, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1178)
    - Board Meeting, December 1, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1179)
    - Board Meeting, December 5, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1180)
    - Board Meeting, December 6, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1181)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 9, Item 1182)
    - Board Meeting, December 8, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1183)
    - Board Meeting, December 10, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1184)
    - Board Meeting, December 15, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1185)
    - Special General Meeting, December 20, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1186)
    - Board Meeting, December 22, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1187)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1945, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1188)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1189)
    - Board Meeting, January 5, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1190)
    - General Meeting, January 9, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1191)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1192)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1193)
    - Board Meeting, January 26, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1194)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1195)
    - Board Meeting, February 2, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1196)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1197)
    - Board Meeting, February 12, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1198)
    - General Meeting, February 13, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1199)
    - Board Meeting, February 16, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1200)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1201)
    - Special General Meeting, February 24, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1202)
    - Board Meeting, February 27, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1203)
    - Board Meeting, February 28, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1204)
    - Board Meeting, March 2, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1205)
    - Board Meeting, March 6, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1206)
    - Board Meeting, March 9, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1207)
    - Board Meeting, March 12, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1208)
    - General Meeting, March 13, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1209)
    - Board Meeting, March 16, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1210)
    - Special General Meeting, March 18, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1211)
    - Board Meeting, March 20, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1212)
    - Board Meeting, March 23, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1213)
    - Board Meeting, March 28, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1214)
    - Board Meeting, March 30, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1215)
    - Board Meeting, April 6, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1216)
    - General Meeting, April 10, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1217)
    - Board Meeting, April 13, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1218)
    - Board Meeting, April 16, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1219)
    - Board Meeting, April 20, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1220)
    - Board Meeting, April 27, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1221)
    - Board Meeting, May 4, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1222)
    - Board Meeting, May 11, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1223)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1224)
    - Board Meeting, May 18, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1225)
    - Board Meeting, May 25, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1226)
    - Board Meeting, May 27, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1227)
    - Board Meeting, June 15, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1228)
    - Board Meeting, June 17, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1229)
    - Board Meeting, June 18, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1230)
    - Board Meeting, June 19, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1231)
    - Board Meeting, June 20, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1232)
    - Board Meeting, June 22, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1233)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1234)
    - Board Meeting, June 27, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1235)
    - Board Meeting, June 29, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1236)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1237)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1238)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1239)
    - Special General Meeting, July 14, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1240)
    - Board Meeting, July 18, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1241)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1242)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1243)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1244)
    - Board Meeting, July 27, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1245)
    - Board Meeting, August 1, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1246)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1247)
    - Board Meeting, August 3, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1248)
    - Board Meeting, August 5, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1249)
    - Board Meeting, August 7, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1250)
    - Board Meeting, August 17, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1251)
    - Special General Meeting, August 18, 1946, 4 leaves (Box 10, Item 1252)
    - Board Meeting, August 24, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1253)
    - Board Meeting, August 28, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1254)
    - Board Meeting, August 31, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1255)
    - Board Meeting, September 7, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1256)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1257)
    - General Meeting, September 11, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1258)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1259)
    - Board Meeting, September 17, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1260)
    - Board Meeting, September 17, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1261)
    - Board Meeting, September 21, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1262)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1263)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1264)
    - General Meeting, October 9, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1265)
    - Board Meeting, October 12, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1266)
    - Board Meeting, October 19, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1267)
    - Board Meeting, October 26, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1268)
    - Board Meeting, November 5, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1269)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1946, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1270)
    - General Meeting, November 13, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1271)
    - Board Meeting, November 13, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1272)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1273)
    - Board Meeting, November 21, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1274)
    - Board Meeting, November 23, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1275)
    - Board Meeting, November 30, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1276)
    - Board Meeting, December 5, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1277)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1278)
    - General Meeting, December 11, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1279)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1280)
    - Board Meeting, December 21, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1281)
    - Board Meeting, December 28, 1946, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1282)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1283)
    - General Meeting, January 8, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1284)
    - Board Meeting, January 8, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1285)
    - Board Meeting, January 11, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1286)
    - Board Meeting, January 18, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1287)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1288)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1289)
    - Board Meeting, February 3, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1290)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1291)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1292)
    - Board Meeting, February 19, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1293)
    - Board Meeting, February 20, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1294)
    - Board Meeting, February 22, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1295)
    - Board Meeting, February 27, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1296)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1297)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1298)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1299)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1300)
    - Board Meeting, March 26, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1301)
    - Board Meeting, March 27, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1302)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1303)
    - Board Meeting, April 3, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1304)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1305)
    - General Meeting, April 9, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1306)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1307)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1308)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1309)
    - Board Meeting, April 22, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1310)
    - Board Meeting, April 25, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1311)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 10, Item 1312)
    - Board Meeting, April 29, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 10, Item 1313)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1314)
    - Board Meeting, May 8, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1315)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1316)
    - General Meeting, May 14, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1317)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1318)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1319)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1320)
    - Board Meeting, May 21, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1321)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1322)
    - Special General Meeting, May 25, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1323)
    - Board Meeting, May 27, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1324)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1325)
    - Board Meeting, June 3, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1326)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1327)
    - Board Meeting, June 7, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1328)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1329)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1330)
    - Board Meeting, July 2, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1331)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1332)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1333)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1334)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1335)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1336)
    - Special General Meeting, August 6, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1337)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1338)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1339)
    - Special General Meeting, August 17, 1947, 3 leaves (Box 11, Item 1340)
    - Board Meeting, August 23, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1341)
    - Board Meeting, August 30, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1342)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1343)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1344)
    - Board Meeting, September 18, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1345)
    - Board Meeting, September 25, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1346)
    - Board Meeting, September 27, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1347)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1348)
    - Special General Meeting, October 5, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1349)
    - General Meeting, October 8, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1350)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1351)
    - Special General Meeting, October 12, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1352)
    - Board Meeting, October 14, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1353)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1354)
    - Board Meeting, October 25, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1355)
    - Board Meeting, November 1, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1356)
    - Special General Meeting, November 13, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1357)
    - Board Meeting, November 15, 1947, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1358)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1359)
    - Board Meeting, November 29, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1360)
    - Board Meeting, December 6, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1361)
    - General Meeting, December 10, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1362)
    - Board Meeting, December 13, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1363)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 17, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1364)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1365)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1947, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1366)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1367)
    - Board Meeting, January 10, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1368)
    - Board Meeting, January 17, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1369)
    - Board Meeting, January 24, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1370)
    - Board Meeting, January 31, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1371)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1948, 3 leaves (Box 11, Item 1372)
    - Board Meeting, February 14, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1373)
    - Special General Meeting, February 20, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1374)
    - Board Meeting, February 21, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1375)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1376)
    - Board Meeting, February 28, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1377)
    - Board Meeting, March 6, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1378)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1379)